Seventh Moon is a horror, thriller film directed by Eduardo Sánchez.
Melissa and Yul, Americans honeymooning in China, come
across the exotic 'Hungry Ghost' festival.
When night falls, the couple end up in a remote village,
and soon realize the legend is all too real.
Plunged into an ancient custom they cannot comprehend, the couple must
find a way to survive the night of the Seventh Moon.
Ping, played by Dennis Chan Kwok-San.
Yul, played by Tim Chiou.
Melissa, played by Amy Smart.
Seventh Moon is a 2008 American horror film written by Eduardo
Sánchez and Jamie Nash, and directed by Eduardo Sánchez.
Part of Robert Tapert's Ghost House Underground DVD
series, and entirely shot in shaky cam style.
The film is based on the Chinese legend that on the full moon of the seventh lunar month,
the gates of hell open and the dead can enter the realm of the living.
It stars Amy Smart as an American woman who is spending her honeymoon
in China with her newlywed Chinese-American husband.
While driving through the countryside the couple gets stranded and
has to find a way to survive the fateful night.
The tone is dark and intense.